Guide to the Dorothy Sarnoff papers, 1920-1998.
Sarnoff, Dorothy Papers, 1920-1998
- Series III. Speech Career
  - A. Correspondence
    - Luv Letters, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Fitzpatrick, Dennis M. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Flaxman, Richard (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Fonseca Ferreira, Jose Carlos (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Fox, Jules J. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Freeman, Lucy (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Friedman, Florence (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Goodman, Betty (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Gregg, Dorothy (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Grove, Brandon, Jr. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Hailey, V. Ann (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Hall, Arthur S. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Hoye, Michael L. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Josefowicz, Barbara Gail (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Kaiser, Edgar F., Jr. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Koch, George W. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Lake, Anthony (signed Tony) (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Lange, Hans Jurgen (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Lett, Lucia (Mrs. Bernard J.) (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Leverson, Helen (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Levine, Phil (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Lewis, Gerald A. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Lieberthal, Mary Louchheim (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Linowitz, Sol M. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Loveland. E.F. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Lubbock, Richard (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - McCarthy, Chris (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - McGreevy, Becky (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - McIntyre, James A. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - McMillen, Eleanor (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - McNutt, C. James (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Merkin, A. Barry (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Meyer, Joan (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Meyers, Gerald C. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Mondale, Joan (Mrs. Fritz) (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Morrissey, Bill (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Murphy, Thomas S. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Nachem?, Rita (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Ogiba, Edward F. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Pecher, Terry (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Penney, Alexandra (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Phillips, W. E. (signed "Bill") (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Pickholz, Jerome W. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Pierce, Albert C. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Price, Robert M. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Qualkinbush, Thom (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Quiunn, A. Peter, Jr. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Reinhardt, John E. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Rhoads, Geraldine (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Roman, Kenneth, Jr. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Rossini, Carlotta (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Rubin, Abby (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Schimel, Ruth M. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Schuker, Jill A. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Singer, Lotte Rockler (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Slootweg, Wim (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Southerland, Barbara (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Spino, Michael (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Stewart, Judy (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Stewart, Robert M. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Stinnett, Carl V. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Sullivan, Humphrey (signed "Sully") (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Van Westering, Karen (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Verne, Richard P. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Vick, Edward H. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Villares, Paulo Diederichsen (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - von Puttkamer, Peter L.K. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Walker, Kenneth (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Weatherwax, Jon (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Weidenfeld, Sheila (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Weiner, Wendy (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Weinflash, Marian (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Wells, Stephen M. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Wennerstrom, Bruce (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Wennerstrom, Genia (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Whitney, William E., Jr. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Wolf, Jeanne (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Woolworth, R.G. (signed "Dick") (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Wooters, J. Dukes, Jr. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Zaepfel, John B. (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Luv Letters, 1980-1983 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Donsky, Barbara von Bracht (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - [Schuler?], Jill (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - [Sinanan?], Inez (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Africano, Lillian (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Bennett, Carrie (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Bentsen, Lloyd (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Berger, Samuel R. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Berman, Barton M. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Biklen, Paul (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Birk, Roger E. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Blinn, Stephan B. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Blum, Bill (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Borowsky, Irvin J. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Bostain, James C. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Branda, Lotte (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Braun, Lissa (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Brescia, Anthony R. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Bromberg. Barbara J. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Brown, Anne (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Burton, Peggy (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - C. James McNutt (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Campbell, William S. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Capp, Irene M. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Carter, John Mack (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Ciatto, Robert J. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Colton, Edward H. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Coyle, Mary Lynn (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Cutler, Howard (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Daverne, Isabelle (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - DeLapa, James P. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Dingman, Michael D. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - DiVito, Paolo G. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Dixon, Barbara S. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Elliott, Jock (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Enos, Sondra Forsyth (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Fergus, Edward T. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Ferguson, Sybil (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Fiori, Pamela (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Foster, Lawrence G. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Foster, Tiah Ann (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Fridl, J.J. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Gilbert, Lynn (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Gilson, Jim (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Grant, Sarah D. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Hands, Venetia (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Harding, Cal (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Hardwick, Charles L. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Hawkes, Carol (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Hentges, Harriet (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Herring, Esther (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Herrman, Anthony A. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Intile, Karen R. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Irving, Flora (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Jacobs, Harry A., Jr. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Jasper, Jay (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Kaplan, Susan J. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Katz, Anthony R. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Kaufman, Rhoda (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Kelly, C. Christine (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Kelly, Daniel Q. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Kirk, Jean M. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Klensch, Ella (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Kraemer, John J. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Lamel, Edward M. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Lane, Robin (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Long, Margro (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Macior, Patricia (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Mackenzie, Iain L., M.D. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Margrabe, William (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Marlantes, L.L. (signed "Lory") (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Mayer, Terry (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - McNutt, C. James (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Meyers, Elizabeth (Signed "Biffie") (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Meyers, Gerald C. (signed "Gerry") (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Michel, Ernest W. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Middleton, W.W., Jr. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Moffat, Anne S. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Moody, Dave (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Moore, Cydelle M. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Munro, Eleanor (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Newell, Gregory J. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Novak, William (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Orci, Roberto (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Ornstein, Jerome Alan (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Paul, Penny (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Penney, Alexandra (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Pool, Mary Jane (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Price, Robert M. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Pruitt, Jean Hampton (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Rand, John (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Reinbolt, Mary G. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Ridings, Dorothy S. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Rineberg, Bernard A. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Roblin, Sara S. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Roman, Kenneth (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Rudisail, H.L. (signed "Lee") (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Samalin, Kay (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Saxton, Catherine P. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Schrode, Tom (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Silber, John R. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Silverman, Marilyn (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Skinner, Charles S. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Smith, Edward S. (signed "Ted") (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Sridhar, R. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Steffey, Wayne A. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Stewart-Gordon, Faith (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Sykes, Martha Moore (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Traina, Cmille and John (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Vaughan, Samuel S. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Vick, Edwin H., Jr. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Voell, Richard A. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Wade, James O'Shea (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Wakin, Edward (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Warren, Peter (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Watson, Robert P. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Weaks, Henry H. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Weiss, Dale (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - West, Benjamin B. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - White, Erwin A. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Wiley, Marie L (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Yockelson, Lisa (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Luv Letters, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - [Borsick, Suffa?] (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - [Feist?], Dorothy (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - [Hale?], Bill (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - [Robins?], Natalie (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - [Shiels?], Kathy (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Abrams, Diane Schulder (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Ashley, Donald D. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Aubert, Lucien (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Avrett, Jack (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Baraz, Bonita (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Bash, Lynne S. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Bookout, John F. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Boston, Margaret A. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Brinn, Carolyn (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Brodeur, Alan R. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Bruce, Doug (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Buden, Jim (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Caperton, Gaston (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Cassidy, William L. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Ciak, Jack (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Clark, Sally (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Conard, Walter E. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Coombs, Joan S. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Cooper, Marcia (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Davis, Norwood H. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - DeNoia, Marie (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Derwent, Robin, Lord ( formerly Robin Johnstone) (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Donski, Barbara (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Dougherty, Roberta (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Duncan, Melba (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Elliott, Tim (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Fanning, Eugene D. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Ferin, Susan (Mrs. Steven) (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Finkbeiner, Horst E. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Friedman, Michael (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Fusella, Julie (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Gallagher, Christine (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Goldberg, Lynn C. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Gordon, Shirley (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Gottlieb, Marilyn (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Gray, Bill (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Greiner, Guenther E. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Harding, Cal (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Harwyn, Barbara (signed "Bobbi") (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Hefferman, Rob (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Hirschen, William (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Holt, Kevin W. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Hrubec, Jane (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Hurst, Gareth R. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Johnson, Robert Wood IV (signed "Woody") (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Juranich, Sharon (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Kallio, Gordon (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Keator, Gerrit M. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Kobacker, Arthur J. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Kronk, Shirley (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Kruger, Paula (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Lamparter, Fred (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Largay, Redmond J. (signed "Ned") (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Latham, Ian (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Leahy, Philip G. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Lowry, Nicholas (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Lucca, Maria (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Maglich, Bogdan C. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Mandel, Jeri (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - McFarren, Ann (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - McPartland, Marian (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - McQuin, Andy (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Miller, Michael C. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Moore, Evelyn T. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Moore, Pamela (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Muscari, Ann (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Nance, C.W. (Wayne) (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Nieuwenhuys, Maarten W. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Nolan, Barbara (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Pierce, Ponchitta (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Randall, Cathy (Mrs. Henry Pettus Randall, III) (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Raphaelson, Joel (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Roth-Dornfield, Mina (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Ruddel, Thomas A. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Ryan, Bernard, Jr. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Sawyer, Blackwell, Jr., M.D. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Sawyer, Diane (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Scavullo, Ann (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Schafran, Lynn Hecht (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Schirn, Janet (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Schirn, Janet (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Scobey, Joan (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Shuman, Audrey L. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Simon, Anne V. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Smith, Manville D., Jr. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Snyder, Jhan (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Spann, Ellen (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Steiner, Therese (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Stringer, Matthew (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Stuart, Robert D., Jr. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Voell, Dick (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Vogelzang, James C. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Volchok, Edward (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Ward, Ashley F. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Westaby, Mark (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Wharton, Dolores (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Wilde, Donald R. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Wisner, Frank G. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Wood, Charles Oaks, III (signed "Chas") (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Wright, Rod (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Zand, Dale (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Luv Letters, 1987-1989 (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - [Mckey?], Michael (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Andruskevich, Thomas A. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Bayless, Pamela (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Bercu, Daniel (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Black, Suzanne (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Brinkman, Peter (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Browning, Elizabeth (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Burns, Jim and Colleen (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Carman, James A. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Chao, Samuel (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Chihaya, Mari (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Curran, M. Kate (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Dam, Kenneth W. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - DeChant, Carol (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - deRogati, Francesco (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Elliott, Gary (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Ellis, David T. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Ferguson, Sybil (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Fidler, Annette (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Glick, Mary (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Goldberg, Lynn C. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Green, Leonard C. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Green, Robert F. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Halligan, Mrs. Theodore (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Hill, Beverly (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Jacobs, Edward L. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Jacobs, Harry A., Jr. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Johnson, Robert Wood, IV (signed "Woody") (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Johnston, Mary (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Juranich, Sharon (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Lindsay, David R. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Lipschitz, Louis (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Magrann, R.P. (signed "Bob") (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Mattson, Gladys (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Mayotte, Mary (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - McConnell, Mary Carter (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - McGonagill, Michael L. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - McKernan, John R., Governor (signed "Jock") (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - McQuilkin, Charlie (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Mirante, Arthur J., II (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Nabers, Mary Scott (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Nanfeldt, Suzan G. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Newby, Thomas A., Jr. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - O'Neill, Patrick F. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - O'Rielly, Curvin (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Ouimet, James M. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Perry, Betsy and Caroline (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Saisho, Yuri (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Schoonover, Jean (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Schroeder, Patricia (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Scott, Daniel T. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Shontell, Jayne J. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Shuart, James M. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Sirianni, Anthony F. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Stein, Zachary D. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Stewart-Gordon, Faith (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Storey, Susan M. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Swartz, Mark H. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Taber, George H. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Tandon, Ranjan (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - van Nispen, Joost (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Verdin, Anne-Marie (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Voell, Dick (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Waller, John W., III (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Webster, Steven E. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Wells, Linda (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Luv Letters, 1990-1997 (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - [Nancy Lee] (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - [Safrio?], Millicent (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Acton, Kipp (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Adams, Mark W. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Andraski, Joseph C. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Ashburn, Jean (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Baird, Allison (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Baker, Angela (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Becket, Joanna (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Behler, Albert P. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Blinken, Vara (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Boyle, Terence K. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Brock, William E. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Burch, Robert L. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Canale, Maria Christin (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Cohen, Steven N. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Cusick, Kate (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Davis, Cliff (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Davis, Scott M. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Dunne, Dominick (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Dunne, Dominick (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Elkins, Robert N. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Eskin, [Eden?] Force (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Feniger, Thomas (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Figliolia, Linda C. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Fisher, Susan G. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Florio, James J. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Foxman, Abraham H. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Frazee, Frank J. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Freemyer, Jeff (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Friedman, Lucy N. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Gaylord, Gail (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Geier, Doris L. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Ginsberg, Janet (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Glass, Daniel S. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Green, Leonard C. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Haas, Joy (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Hagan, Marisa M. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Hagmayer, Barbara (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Harris, Caroline (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Heltai, Marianne (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Heltai, Marianne (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Hilton, John (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Hopson, Marissa (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Huff, Robert B.V. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Hurt, Floyd (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Istona, Mildred (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Jacobs, Harry A., Jr. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Jacobson, Marshall M. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Joseph, Judith (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Kane, Mary E. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Kennedy, Raymond M. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Kenny,Deborah A. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Knall, David W. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Knox, Hubbard A., III (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Kolanko, Wayne (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Lalli, Frank (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Larsen, Ralph S. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Levy, Walter (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Lewis, Loida Nicholas (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Lilley, Kristen (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Lucas, Jim (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Martini, William J. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Master, Helen (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - McClellan, Max (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Meuleman, Robert J. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Meuleman, Robert J. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Miller, Anthony R. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Morrell, Margot (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Paley, Bettina (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Paolino, Joseph R., Jr. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Pfister, Jack (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Pielou, Adriaane (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Platt, Helen Brightrall (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Richardella, Lillie (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Richardson, Albert T. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Robinson, Harry A. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Rogers, Leo J., Jr. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Scavullo, Ann (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Sherlock, Valerie (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Sidamon-Eristoff, Anne (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Siebert, Deborah S. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Simon, Penny (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Singer, Francis (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Slocum, George S. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Slonim, Roberta, M.D. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Spiro, Rachel (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Stein, Zachary D. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Stern, Susan (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Strauss, Gregory J. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Stundis, Linda Cody (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Tretheway, Barton G. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Tway, Patricia (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Van Den Hout, Tjaco T. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Voell, Dick (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Wells, Linda (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Wharton, Dolores (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Wigand, Patricia A. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Wilson, Felicia (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Witteman, Marla (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - B. Clippings
    - Clippings, 1966-1970 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Clippings, 1971-1976 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Clippings, 1977-1986 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Clippings, 1989-1998 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Clippings 1963-1992 (Box 38, Folder 11-12)
  - C. Photographs
    - First Speech Class, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 144)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff on "Claire" show, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 140)
    - Photograph of Dorothy Sarnoff (Box 5, Folder 141)
    - Photograph of Dorothy Sarnoff (Box 5, Folder 142)
    - Photograph of Dorothy Sarnoff (Box 5, Folder 143)
    - Photographs of Dorothy Sarnoff and others (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Slide of Dorothy Sarnoff demonstrating NY accent - NY Daily News Sunday News (Box 26)
  - D. Administrative and Advertising Material
    - NY Times ad layout for Speech Cosmetics, ca. 1967 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Advertisements for Speech Cosmetics, 1967-1970 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Brochure Materials, ca. 1970-1979 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Brochure Materials, ca. 1970-1979 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Proposal offering Speech Dynamics Inc. services to Central Intelligence Agency, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Contract/permission form for Ed Sullivan Show 1992 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Speech Cosmetics letterhead (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Speech Dynamics "kit" and brochure (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Speech Dynamics Book I (notebook) (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Speech Dynamics Book II (notebook) (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Speech Dynamics accounts (notebook) 1983-1988 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Speech Dynamics notes (notebook) (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Appointment book 1974 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Appointment books (3) 1975 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Appointment book 1977 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Appointment book 1978 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Appointment books 1981-1984 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Appointment books 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 24)